HERE Audio-Visual Materials 6199 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Audio-Visual Materials
1977-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199 AV
16.33 cubic feet
16.3 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
7721515
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 08, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Scope and Contents
The majority of the tapes in the collection date to the late 1980's and 1990's, with a small number of tapes covering the 1950's, 60's, and 70's and a substantial number from the early 2000's. Productions vary from public service announcements, television news reports, convention tapes, Senate hearings, and commercial productions, about, for, and against HERE and the labor movement.
Key players represented include General President Edward Hanley, General President John Wilhelm, Executive Director Ron Richardson, Reverend Jesse Jackson, and Local 226 and 165 of Las Vegas.
There are two overall themes in the collection:
1. HERE conventions and Executive Board meetings, along with the various films that are shown to the delegates.
2. The organizing campaigns, struggles, and victories of the union in Las Vegas and the west coast, in particular the Frontier Hotel and Casino strike.
The collection include a series of anti-union and union busting films about tactics and tools they employ to either defeat a union in the election process or decertify it. Tapes also document tactics and techniques that organizers employ to recruit new members, to engage existing members, and to build support for the goals of the particular campaign. In addition, tapes examine a connection between HERE and organized crime.
There are also music videos made by workers for the union including songs of union solidarity, films about arrest procedures and best practices for a non-violet sit in, commercial productions about how union members have helped children of other countries live better, in particular those in Mexico. There are also introductory videos and presentations about other unions including the Sheet Metal Workers International Allegiance (SMWIA), United Food and Commercial Workers (UFCW), and The American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6199 G: HERE Graphics 6199 MB: HERE Memorabilia 6199 mf: HERE Records on Microfilm 6199 PUBS: HERE Publications 6199/001: HERE Legislative Department Files 6199/002: HERE Western Region Local Files 6199/003: HERE Organizing Department Las Vegas Strike Files 6199/003 mf: HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/004: HERE Locals files 6199/004 mf: HERE Locals Files on Microfilm 6199/005: HERE Communications Department Files 6199/005 P: HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/006: HERE General Executive Board Files 6199/006 mf: HERE General Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/007 mf: HERE Financial Records Files on Microfilm 6199/008 mf: HERE General President's Files on Microfilm 6199/009 mf: HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm 6199/010 mf: HERE General Office Legal Files on Microfilm 6199/011 mf: HERE Official Journals on Microfilm 6199/012 mf: HERE Joint Executive Board Files on Microfilm 6199/013: HERE Historical Files 6199/013 P: HERE Historical Photographs 6199/014: HERE Conventions Files 6199/015: HERE Editor Files
Hospitality industry--Employees--Labor unions; Hotels--Employees--Labor unions; Restaurants--Employees--Labor unions; Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union
7721515
- HEREIU, General Executive Board, August 22-25, 1999, Vancouver, B.C. Canada, 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  tape 1 of 9
- HEREIU, General Executive Board, August 22-25, 1999, Vancouver, B.C. Canada, 2 (Box 1)
  tape 2 of 9
- HEREIU, General Executive Board, August 22-25, 1999, Vancouver, B.C. Canada, 3 (Box 1)
  tape 3 of 9
- HEREIU, General Executive Board, August 22-25, 1999, Vancouver, B.C. Canada, 4 (Box 1)
  tape 4 of 9
- HEREIU, General Executive Board, August 22-25, 1999, Vancouver, B.C. Canada, 5 (Box 1)
  tape 5 of 9
- HEREIU, General Executive Board, August 22-25, 1999, Vancouver, B.C. Canada, 6 (Box 1)
  tape 6 of 9
- HEREIU, General Executive Board, August 22-25, 1999, Vancouver, B.C. Canada, 7 (Box 1)
  tape 7 of 9
- HEREIU, General Executive Board, August 22-25, 1999, Vancouver, B.C. Canada, 8 (Box 1)
  tape 8 of 9
- HEREIU, General Executive Board, August 22-25, 1999, Vancouver, B.C. Canada, 9 (Box 1)
  tape 9 of 9
- Marriott, Tape #1 - 1997, 10 (Box 1)
- Marriott, Local 2, Tape #2 - 1997, 11 (Box 1)
- Marriott, Local 2 - Tape #3 - 1997, 12 (Box 1)
- Marriott, Local 2 - Tape #4 - 1997, 13 (Box 1)
- Marriott, Local 2 - Tape #6 - 1998, 14 (Box 1)
- Marriott, Local 2 - Tape #7 - 1998, 15 (Box 1)
- Marriott, Local 2 - Tape #8 - 1998, 16 (Box 1)
- Marriott, Local 2 - Tape #9 - 1998, 17 (Box 1)
- Marriott, Local 2 - Tape #10 - 1998, 18 (Box 1)
- HEREIU, General Executive Board Meeting -- August 22-25, 1999, Vancouver, B.C. Canada, 19 (Box 1)
  Sunday: LSG/Sky Chefs & Barbeque
- Local Marriott - Tape #1A - Outtakes from Summer/Fall 1997, 20 (Box 1)
- One Day Longer: the Story of the Frontier Strike, 21 (Box 1)
- One Day Longer: the Story of the Frontier Strike, 22 (Box 1)
- One Day Longer: the Story of the Frontier Strike, 23 (Box 1)
- Looking Back Moving Forward, 24 (Box 1)
  (2 copies of this on CD-ROM were removed and placed in the CD/DVD cabinet
- UNITE 2003, 25 (Box 1)
- UNITE 2003, 26 (Box 1)
- UNITE 2003, 27 (Box 1)
- GEB - 6/18 #2, 28 (Box 1)
- Wilhelm Addresses HERE Exec. Board - 2/24/2004, 29 (Box 1)
- Local 21 - Hotel, Hospital, Restaurant and Tavern Employees Union, 1999; 30 (Box 1)
- Wilhelm Addresses HERE Exec. Board, 31 (Box 1)
- Wilhelm Addresses HERE Exec. Board, 32 (Box 1)
- Local 54, HERE for you -- March 9, 1995, 1 (Box 2)
- Local 54, HERE for you -- March 9, 1995, 2 (Box 2)
- Americans at work, 3 (Box 2)
- We Serve the Public, 4 (Box 2)
- HERE Historical and 1991 Convention Highlights - 10/18/1991, 5 (Box 2)
- Box Tree - Food News - 1996, 6 (Box 2)
- HERE, Politics: Behind the Scenes, 7 (Box 2)
- Vegas Strike - 4/2/1984 // 10 days as of 4/11/1984, 8 (Box 2)
- Americans at work, 9 (Box 2)
- Hanley Banquet - 8/9/1998, 10 (Box 2)
- HEREIU - FLALU #55 -- Right to Work - Org., 11 (Box 2)
- GEB -- 6/17 #1, 12 (Box 2)
- HERE Local 57 - 11/5/1996, 13 (Box 2)
  Members to the Polls on the buses
- Hotel, Motel and Restaurant, Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 471 - AFL-CIO, 14 (Box 2)
- Hotel, Motel & Restaurant, Employees & Bartenders Union, Local 471 - AFL-CIO, 15 (Box 2)
- HERE General Executive Board Meeting -- June 18-19, 1997, 16 (Box 2)
  tape 4 of 5
- Amtrak - On-Board Service, 17 (Box 2)
- Culinary Union 226 / Rich Trumka, 18 (Box 2)
- Hotel Stack the Deck - Union Busting in Las Vegas, 19 (Box 2)
- Las Vegas: Summer 89 -- Hotter than ever, 20 (Box 2)
- Local 483 - The Hotel Workers Justice March -- 9/25/1998, 21 (Box 2)
- Special Rally Local 483 -- Asilomar Workers -- 10/13/1998, 22 (Box 2)
- Fighting for our union, 23 (Box 2)
- Culinary / John Ralston Talking 3/12/1990, 24 (Box 2)
- Turning Point: Justice at the Horseshoe, 25 (Box 2)
  Culinary Workers Local 226 & Bartenders Local 165
- Culinary Workers Local 226 - MacNeil Lehrer MGM/Culinary 3/2/1994; Factfinding - 3/2/1994 Report, 26 (Box 2)
- Box Tree Strikers, 27 (Box 2)
- Culinary Workers Union Local 226 - Frontier Strike - 3rd Year Anniversary, September 21, 1994, 28 (Box 2)
- Vegas Worseshoe, 29 (Box 2)
- We do the work - Show #306, 30 (Box 2)
- John Frogue - Bartenders Union 165, 31 (Box 2)
- Jesse Jackson @ Detroit Westin Birthday Party - 10/30/1991, 32 (Box 2)
- Fighting for our union: an indignant EYE Production for HERE Local 75, 33 (Box 2)
- Jesse Jackson @ Detroit Westin Birthday Party -- 10/21/1991, 34 (Box 2)
- HERE Hearing - 7/21/1999 -- #6, 1 (Box 3)
- HERE Hearing - 7/21/1999 -- #3, 2 (Box 3)
- HERE Hearing - 7/21/1999 -- #5, 3 (Box 3)
- HERE Hearing -- 7/21/1999 --- #4, 4 (Box 3)
- HERE Hearing -- 7/21/1999 -- #2, 5 (Box 3)
- HERE Hearing -- 7/21/1999 -- #1, 6 (Box 3)
- Turning Point - Justice at the Horseshoe -- Culinary Workers Local 226 & Bartenders Local 165, 7 (Box 3)
- We're the ones, 8 (Box 3)
- Civil Disobedience at the Frontier Hotel, September 7, 1992 - Labor Day, Culinary Workers Local 226, 9 (Box 3)
- Culinary Workers Union 226 -- 12/3-5/1992; Solidarity March "Line in the Sand", 10 (Box 3)
- The Fifth Estate -- HERE Union Locals 31, 40 & 75, 11 (Box 3)
- Fighting for our union, 12 (Box 3)
  Indignant Eye Productions
- Culinary/Frontier Picket Line Incident -- 68 cuts from 4/28-5/9/1993, 13 (Box 3)
  tape 1 of 2
- Culinary Workers Union #226 - Take Back our Sidewalks, 14 (Box 3)
  Moonstar Productions
- Culinary/Frontier Picket Line Incident -- 68 cuts from 4/28-5/9/1993, 15 (Box 3)
  tape 2 of 2
- Vegas Strike -- 4/2/1984; 10 days as of 4/11/1984, 16 (Box 3)
- Leaving Home, 17 (Box 3)
  We Do the Work
- Sexual Harassment - Summit '99 -- HERE loc. 75, 18 (Box 3)
- Sexual Harassment - Summit '99 -- HERE loc. 75, 19 (Box 3)
- Phil Ruffin: the New Frontier, 20 (Box 3)
- Desert Solidarity (National Support for Frontier Strikers), Las Vegas, Nevada -- December 5, 1992, 21 (Box 3)
- Holiday Inn -- Philly -- Rev. J. Jackson Rally, 22 (Box 3)
- Interviews with Marchers - Local 226, 23 (Box 3)
- Dining Car Workers, 24 (Box 3)
- Building Better Lives for Union America, 25 (Box 3)
- Para su Beneficio -- Hotel & Restaurant Employees Health Fund, 26 (Box 3)
- HERE TIP, 27 (Box 3)
- Las Vegas Cocktail Waitresses, 28 (Box 3)
- Culinary Workers Union Local 226 - MGM Grand Rally -- 5/19-27/1994, 29 (Box 3)
- Your Health Care Alternative, 30 (Box 3)
- HERE Informational Video Production - Communications World Corp. -- 8/18/1983, 31 (Box 3)
- Las Vegas Hotel Strike, 32 (Box 3)
- HERE Politics: Behind the Scenes, 33 (Box 3)
- HERE Politics: Behind the Scenes, 34 (Box 3)
- HERE General Executive Board Meeting - June 18-19, 1997, 1 (Box 4)
  tape 2 of 5
- HERE General Executive Board Meeting -- June 18-19, 1997, 2 (Box 4)
- HERE General Executive Board Meeting -- June 18-19, 1997, 3 (Box 4)
  tape 1 of 5
- HERE General Executive Board Meeting -- June 18-19, 1997, 4 (Box 4)
- Abuse of Privilege, 5 (Box 4)
- HERE General Executive Board Meeting -- June 18-19, 1997, 6 (Box 4)
  tape 5 of 5
- HERE General Executive Board Meeting -- June 18-19, 1997, 7 (Box 4)
- HERE General Executive Board Meeting -- June 18-19, 1997, 8 (Box 4)
- HERE General Executive Board meeting -- June 18-19, 1997, 9 (Box 4)
  tape 3 of 5
- HERE General Executive Board Meeting -- June 18-19, 1997, 10 (Box 4)
- Local 25 -- At your service (11/9/1995) -- I was fired and the Union got me my job back, 11 (Box 4)
- Governor's -- 3/14/1986, 12 (Box 4)
- Organizing Unions: the Catholic Perspective, 13 (Box 4)
- Local 21 -- Hotel, Hospital, Restaurant and Tavern Employees Union, 1999; 14 (Box 4)
- At your service - Irish exchange 1988, 15 (Box 4)
- Ohama Lokali: Convention and 1990 Strike, 16 (Box 4)
- Struggle for dignity, 17 (Box 4)
- Above the law, 18 (Box 4)
- Victor Josie, 19 (Box 4)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 20 (Box 4)
  Political Action Video - UNITE
- Local 5 - Orientation Video, 21 (Box 4)
- Culinary Workers Union 226 -- 12/3-5/1992; Solidarity March "Line in the sand", 22 (Box 4)
- Announcement of Concessions Division Sale, November 1986, 23 (Box 4)
  Corporate Communications Video Library
- Culinary Union Local 226; AFSCME Solidarity March, June 18, 1992, 24 (Box 4)
- Ohana Lokahi: Local 5 Convention & Local 5 Strike 1990, 1993; 25 (Box 4)
- HERE Union Show #1, 26 (Box 4)
- Union Busting "Investigate" - 1996 Convention, 27 (Box 4)
- People have the power: building the Union in San Francisco, 28 (Box 4)
- Ohana Lokahi: Local 5 Convention & Local 5 Strike 1990, 1993; 29 (Box 4)
- Events at Coastal Berry Co. - July 2, 1998, 30 (Box 4)
- Captive Audience Meeting, 31 (Box 4)
- Restoring employees rights is good for America, 1993; 32 (Box 4)
- Local 5 Orientation, 33 (Box 4)
- In-House Polling: A new technique for organizing VHS, 34 (Box 4)
- Local 25 - At your service (11/9/1995); I was fired and the Union got me my job back, 35 (Box 4)
- Galludet - Going in on the Boss: Building the Committee, 36 (Box 4)
- Local 25: Galludet Prayer Meeting (Part I & II), 37 (Box 4)
- Culinary/Frontier Strike - Jessie Jackson -- 10/11/1991, 1 (Box 5)
- Culinary Dispute - Dub of First Tape/Hotels, 2 (Box 5)
- Labor Secretary Alexis Herman visits the Culinary Union Training Center, Las Vegas on November 22, 1997, 3 (Box 5)
- Frontier Presentation: Day 2, 4 (Box 5)
  tape 4 & 5
- Frontier Rally & Speech -- 10/11/1991 -- Jesse Jackson, 5 (Box 5)
- Culinary Local 226 - Labor Day & Appeals Court Ruling -- 9/4 & 9/8/1995, 6 (Box 5)
- CNN 2/12/1996 - Las Vegas -- Taylor, Sweeney, 7 (Box 5)
- Hanley Banquet --- 8/9/1998, 8 (Box 5)
- Clinton Visits Las Vegas; Intro. By Maggie Carlton, 9 (Box 5)
- Culinary Workers Union Local 226 -- March and Rally in Downtown Las Vegas -- August 10, 1994, 10 (Box 5)
- Culinary Workers Union Local 226 -- March and Rally in Downtown Las Vegas -- August 10, 1994, 11 (Box 5)
- Political and Legislative Conference: Grand Ballroom Speakers -- HERE Intl. Union, 12 (Box 5)
  tape 3 of 3
- Political and Legislative Conference: Grand Ballroom Speakers -- HERE Intl. Union, 13 (Box 5)
- Political and Legislative Conference: Grand Ballroom Speakers -- HERE Intl. Union, 14 (Box 5)
- Capitol Hill Hearing -- HERE - 7/21/1999, 15 (Box 5)
  tapes 1-4 - Window Dub
- Capitol Hill Hearing -- HERE - 7/21/1999, 16 (Box 5)
  tapes 5 & 6
- Executive Board Meeting - HERE Intl. Union, 17 (Box 5)
- Executive Board Meeting - HERE Intl. Union, 18 (Box 5)
  tape #2 of 5
- Executive Board Meeting - HERE Intl. Union, 19 (Box 5)
  tape #3 of 5
- HERE Executive Board Meeting, 20 (Box 5)
  tape #4 of 5
- HERE Intl. Union Executive Board Meeting, 21 (Box 5)
  tape #5 of 5
- HERE Historical and 1991 Convention Highlights - 10/18/1991, 22 (Box 5)
- HERE Historical and 1991 Convention Highlights -- 10/18/1991, 23 (Box 5)
- Galludet vote count/party, 24 (Box 5)
- Local 25 - Galludet Prayer Meeting (edited version), 25 (Box 5)
- Local 25 - Dr. Lee - 2/25/1987, 26 (Box 5)
- Galludet Speak-out (Proposal Meeting) - 2/18/1997, 27 (Box 5)
- Interviews - Debbie Mac/Jackie/Sterling, 28 (Box 5)
- The Union Game: Beating the Union Busters, 29 (Box 5)
- Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees - Organizing, 30 (Box 5)
- HERE Members with Rep. L. Sanches; HERE Members at U.M.W Rally, 31 (Box 5)
- Missionaries for the union, 32 (Box 5)
- HERE Historical and 1991 Convention Highlights -- 10/18/1991, 33 (Box 5)
- The Little Cafeteria of Horrors, 34 (Box 5)
- Abuse of privilege, 1 (Box 6)
- Hotel Del footage highlights, 2 (Box 6)
  copy 2
- Hotel Del Footage Highlights, 3 (Box 6)
  copy 1
- David Winters "Strangers on the right" HERE, 4 (Box 6)
- AFL-CIO Immigration Committee Mtg. -- 4/18/2001, 5 (Box 6)
- Hogar De Los Ninos - December 14-15, 2002, 6 (Box 6)
- HERE President John W. Wilhelm addresses HERE Executive Board - 2/24/2004, 7 (Box 6)
- HERE President John W. Wilhelm addresses HERE Executive Board - 2/24/2004, 8 (Box 6)
- HERE President John W. Wilhelm addresses HERE Executive Board - 2/24/2004, 9 (Box 6)
- 21st Century Workforce Summit - June 20th, 2001, 10 (Box 6)
- 21 st Century Workforce Summit - June 20th, 2001, 11 (Box 6)
- Culinary Workers Union #226 - Take back our sidewalks, 12 (Box 6)
- Testimony of Culinary Workers Union Local 226, 1998; 13 (Box 6)
  National Gambling Impact Study Commission; Las Vegas, November 10-11, 1998
- Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride - Highlights July 2003, 14 (Box 6)
- People have the power; building the Union in San Francisco, 15 (Box 6)
- & Spa Workers Unite, 16 (Box 6)
- Ohana Lokahi: Local 5 Convention & Local 5 Strike 1990, 1993; 17 (Box 6)
- Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride - Highlights July 2003, 18 (Box 6)
- Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union; 43rd General Convention - New Voices, New Directions, 19 (Box 6)
  The Highlights
- No one stands alone - The Hilton Victory - 12/6/2002, 20 (Box 6)
  Review copy
- Chicago Hotel Contract 2002 - Fox News with Walter Jacobson - Channel 32 - February 21, 2002, 21 (Box 6)
- Hotel Del Footage Highlights, 22 (Box 6)
  copy 3
- Victory is ours! The Frontier Strikers win in Las Vegas, 23 (Box 6)
- Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride - Highlights July 2003, 24 (Box 6)
- Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union - 43rd General Convention- "New Voices, New Directions, 25 (Box 6)
- At Your Service - Show #208 - Battle in Seattle - Round 2 - DC 3/2/2000, 26 (Box 6)
- Hotels stack the deck - Vegas, 27 (Box 6)
- Abuse of Privilege, 28 (Box 6)
- Ohana Lokahi: Local 5 Convention & Local 5 Strike 1990, 1993; 29 (Box 6)
- HERE 681 - at the Disneyland Resort -- November 5, 2003, 30 (Box 6)
- Culinary Local 777 - Cut 1-30 Sec Commercial; Cut 2-Message from Las Vegas -- May 1994, 31 (Box 6)
- Local 99 - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union, 32 (Box 6)
- The Case of the Grieving Waitress - Center for Labor Research and Education, 33 (Box 6)
- HERE Yale Rally - May 27, 1996 - Revised, 34 (Box 6)
- Vegas Strike - 4/2/1984; 10 days as of 4/11/1984, 35 (Box 6)
- Hotels Stack the deck: Union-busting in Las Vegas, 36 (Box 6)
- Executive Board Mtg. - 3/5/1999 -- Technology Report and Budget Report, 1 (Box 7)
- Building Bridges - v. 1, 1997; 2 (Box 7)
- 5Y - HERE for you -- 10/5/1995, 3 (Box 7)
- Sexual Harassment - Summit '99; HERE loc. 75, 1999; 4 (Box 7)
- Turning Point - Justice at the Horseshoe; Culinary Workers Local 226 & Bartenders Local 165, 5 (Box 7)
- "America Needs a Raise" Town Meeting Compilation, Columbus, Ohio - 4/30/1996, 6 (Box 7)
  Switched feed compilation, tapes 1 & 2
- Union International #2, 7 (Box 7)
- Union International #1, 8 (Box 7)
- We're the ones, 9 (Box 7)
  Indignant EYE Productions
- Edward T. Hanley Appreciation Video - HEREIU 43rd General Convention, 10 (Box 7)
- Edward T. Hanley Appreciation Video - HEREIU 43rd General Convention, 11 (Box 7)
- Celebrating the New Atlantic City - 20th Anniversary of Casino Gaming -- July 1997, 12 (Box 7)
- HERE Int'l. Union - Political and Legislative Conference - Grand Ballroom Speakers, 13 (Box 7)
  tape #2 of 4
- HERE Int'l. Union - Political and Legislative Conference - Grand Ballroom Speakers, 14 (Box 7)
  tape #1 of 4
- HERE Int'l. Union - Political and Legislative Conference - Grand Ballroom Speakers, 15 (Box 7)
- HERE Int'l. Union - Political and Legislative Conference - Grand Ballroom Speakers, 16 (Box 7)
  tape #3 of 4
- Winnipeg Interview, 17 (Box 7)
- Antony Tynes, 18 (Box 7)
- The Road Wasn't Easy II - Antony Tynes, 19 (Box 7)
- Williams Interview, 20 (Box 7)
- Williams Interview, 21 (Box 7)
- "Broken Promise" - Version 1-"America the Beautiful"; version 1-Above-Tied, 22 (Box 7)
- HERE "Organizing" - 6/10/1991, 23 (Box 7)
- SMWIA - "Intro. The SMWIA" - 11/21/1986, 24 (Box 7)
- HERE Int'l. Union - Political and Legislative Conference - Grand Ballroom Speakers, 25 (Box 7)
  tape #2 of 3
- HERE Int'l. Union - Political and Legislative Conference - Grand Ballroom Speakers, 26 (Box 7)
  tape #1 of 3
- HERE Int'l. Union - Political and Legislative Conference - Grand Ballroom Speakers, 27 (Box 7)
  tape #4 of 4
- Capitol Meeting & Planning - 6/16/1987, 28 (Box 7)
- UFCW Local 400 - "The Road to Dignity" - 7/17/1990, 29 (Box 7)
- Maurer Anderson & Conway "To Dream", 30 (Box 7)
- HERE Int'l. Union - Political and Legislative Conference - Grand Ballroom Speakers, 31 (Box 7)
- HERE Int'l. Union - Political and Legislative Conference - Grand Ballroom Speakers, 32 (Box 7)
- HERE Int'l. Union - Political and Legislative Conference - Grand Ballroom Speakers, 33 (Box 7)
- Justice for janitors SEIU, 1 (Box 8)
  CD training
- Let Justice Roll Down - The Working Poor: Challenge to the Religious Community, 2 (Box 8)
- HERE Video #3 - for readers only, 3 (Box 8)
- Job Security and Strikes: Your future in the union's hands, 4 (Box 8)
  video 4
- Collective Bargaining: The Party's Over - English, 5 (Box 8)
- Let Justice Roll Down - The Working Poor: Challenge to the Religious Community, 6 (Box 8)
- Miramar Sheraton: 25 hour, 7 (Box 8)
  Spanish
- Frontier Strike Over: Speeches and walk-in, 8 (Box 8)
  tape 1 of 3
- Frontier Strike Over: Speeches and walk-in - 1/31/1998, 9 (Box 8)
  tape 2 of 3
- Frontier Strike Over: Speeches and walk-in 1/31/1998, 10 (Box 8)
- Union Summer, 11 (Box 8)
- Victory is ours: frontier strike, 12 (Box 8)
- 1999 AFL-CIO Convention - Remarks by John Wilhelm; Monday, October 11, 13 (Box 8)
- Union Strikes: a lot on the line, 14 (Box 8)
  English
- Collective Bargaining: Party's over, 15 (Box 8)
- Collective Bargaining: The Union Gamble, 16 (Box 8)
  video 2
- Collective Bargaining: the Party's over, 17 (Box 8)
- Taking on the new Otani, 18 (Box 8)
- Collective Bargaining: The Party's over, 19 (Box 8)
- Yale Strike Video, 20 (Box 8)
- 1999 AFL-CIO Convention - Indian Gambling -- Monday, October 11, 21 (Box 8)
- Election Day - Participation and Choice, 22 (Box 8)
  video 5
- AFSCME - Day 2, 1998, 23 (Box 8)
- Union Strikes: A lot on the Line, 24 (Box 8)
- Union Strikes: A lot of the Line, 25 (Box 8)
- Union Summer 1997, 26 (Box 8)
  Recruitment Video
- Evelyn - Promises, 27 (Box 8)
- Taking on new Otani, 28 (Box 8)
- Testimony of Culinary - Workers Union Local 226, 29 (Box 8)
- Tultex Captive, 30 (Box 8)
- HERE/Local 27 - Intv's 1 - Washington, DC, 31 (Box 8)
- HERE - John Wilhelm - Speaks at "99 Convention, LA", 32 (Box 8)
- Local 27 - Dub from VHS - Union Meeting footage, 33 (Box 8)
- Local 27 - Central Parking Demonstration, 34 (Box 8)
  Off-Loading buses at New Have; footage of New Haven Rally
- Local 27 - Rally; news clips; union meeting, 35 (Box 8)
- HERE Local 27 - InterParking Picket, 36 (Box 8)
  more picket Brdl & ending speeches; Interview: Roxie Herbeklan, Pres.; tape 2
- HERE Local 27 - Intv's: Abere Belay -- 6/13/2000, 37 (Box 8)
- HERE Local 27 - Intv's -- 5/17/2000, 38 (Box 8)
  tape 2
- HERE - Parking - b-roll -- 5/2/2000, 39 (Box 8)
- Local 27 - Union Mtg. - Demonstration, 40 (Box 8)
  Dub from VHS
- HERE Local 27 - InterParking Picket @ 1920, 41 (Box 8)
  tape 1
- HERE News & Rally Clips, 42 (Box 8)
- Canada - G. Wilson, 1 (Box 9)
- HERE Convention, 2 (Box 9)
  Tuesday July 5
- HERE Convention, 1991; 3 (Box 9)
  Tuesday - July 9, 1991
- HERE Convention, 4 (Box 9)
  Tuesday - July 9
- HERE Convention, 1991; 5 (Box 9)
  Tuesday -- July 9, 1991
- HERE Convention, 6 (Box 9)
  Monday - July 8
- HERE Convention, 1991; 7 (Box 9)
  July 8, 1991
- HERE Convention, 1991; 8 (Box 9)
  Monday, July 8, 1991
- HERE Convention, 9 (Box 9)
- HERE Convention, 10 (Box 9)
- HERE Convention, 1991; 11 (Box 9)
- HERE Convention, 12 (Box 9)
  July 8
- HERE Convention, 13 (Box 9)
- HERE Convention, 14 (Box 9)
- Sat. #4 - AU/PU, 1 (Box 10)
- Sat #5, 2 (Box 10)
- Sat #1, 3 (Box 10)
- Thr. #3, 4 (Box 10)
- Thr. #4, 5 (Box 10)
- Fri #3, 6 (Box 10)
- Fri #7, 7 (Box 10)
- Fri #6, 8 (Box 10)
- Fri #5, 9 (Box 10)
- Fri #4, 10 (Box 10)
- Fri #2, 11 (Box 10)
- Fri #1, 12 (Box 10)
- Thr. #2, 13 (Box 10)
- Thr. #1, 14 (Box 10)
- Sat #3, 15 (Box 10)
- Sat #2, 16 (Box 10)
- Vegas Hotel Strike, 1 (Box 11)
- Out of the Shadows: a story from the heart of working America, 2 (Box 11)
- Out of the Shadows: a story from the heart of working America, 3 (Box 11)